en

Products

For Individuals

For Companies

* About

English

Products

Back

* Icon / @64 px / Single / Swiss Quality About

* For Individuals

* For Companies

General Privacy Policy
======================

for the Threema Website

General
-------

With this General Privacy Policy, we want to give you an overview over the processing of your personal data in relation with visiting and interacting with the “**Threema Website**” ([https://threema.ch/](https://threema.ch/)).

Detailed information about data protection when visiting and interacting with the Threema Website can be found [here](https://threema.ch/en/privacy-policy).

Who is responsible for processing personal data?
------------------------------------------------

Threema GmbH, Churerstrasse 82, 8808 Pfäffikon SZ, Switzerland, is responsible for the processing of personal data. You can contact our Data Protection Officer at `privacy at threema dot ch`.

What purposes does Threema process personal data for?
-----------------------------------------------------

We process your personal data for the following purposes:

* Delivery of the Threema Website;
* Recording, processing, and answering of support requests, feedback, and business inquiries (voluntary and optional);
* Carrying-out of prize draws (voluntary and optional);
* Public relations (voluntary and optional);
* Marketing;
* Marketing analysis (only for business customers);
* Information security.

What personal data is processed?
--------------------------------

When visiting the Threema Website, the following personal data is processed:

* IP address.

Depending on how you interact with the Threema Website, we process the following personal data if you voluntarily provide and submit it:

* First name;
* Last name;
* Company;
* Domicile address;
* Country;
* Email address;
* Telephone number;
* Customer status.

What personal data is stored and for how long?
----------------------------------------------

The following personal data is stored by us (storage period in brackets):

* IP address (for 10 days in logfiles and only if an error occurs when calling up the Threema Website);
* First name (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 15 months or until revocation);
* Last name (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 15 months or until revocation);
* Company (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 15 months or until revocation);
* Domicile address (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 15 months or until revocation);
* Country (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 15 months or until revocation);
* Email address (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 12 months or until revocation);
* Telephone number (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 12 months or until revocation);
* Customer status (in principle for a maximum of 6 to 12 months or until revocation).

Is personal data disclosed to third parties?
--------------------------------------------

We make every effort to process the personal data that occurs when using the Threema Website exclusively on our own hardware (servers) in Switzerland.

The following companies located in Switzerland and the EU/EEA are commissioned by us as processors:

* In order for you to register for and participate in webinars, Livestorm SAS located in France processes the first name, last name, company, country, email address and customer status.

Is personal data collected from third parties?
----------------------------------------------

Principally, Threema does not collect any personal data from third parties.

The following personal data is collected by Threema from companies located in Switzerland and the EU/EEA:

For advertising by letter mail towards business customers (not private individuals or consumers in general), Threema collects from Dun & Bradstreet Schweiz AG, located in Switzerland, the first name, last name, company, domicile address, and country.

What rights do you have?
------------------------

You have a right to information to Threema and a right to rectification, completion, deletion, and blocking of your personal data as well as a right to withdrawal (of your consent) and to objection (against data processing based on overriding interests).

Products[Overview](https://threema.ch/en "Overview")[Threema](https://threema.ch/en/secure-messenger "Threema")[Threema Work](https://threema.ch/en/work/business-messenger "Threema Work")[Threema Broadcast](https://threema.ch/en/broadcast "Threema Broadcast")[Threema OnPrem](https://threema.ch/en/onprem "Threema OnPrem")[Threema Gateway](https://threema.ch/en/gateway "Threema Gateway")

Threema[Features](https://threema.ch/en/features "Features")[Security](https://threema.ch/en/security "Security")[What’s New](https://threema.ch/en/whats-new "What’s New")[Download](https://threema.ch/en/download "Download")

Resources[FAQs](https://threema.ch/en/support "FAQs")[Messenger Comparison](https://threema.ch/en/messenger-comparison "Messenger Comparison")[WhatsApp Alternative](https://threema.ch/en/why-threema "WhatsApp Alternative")[Forrester Wave™: Secure Communications Solutions 2024](https://threema.ch/en/work/forrester-2024 "Forrester Wave™: Secure Communications Solutions 2024")[Cryptography Whitepaper](https://threema.ch/press-files/2_documentation/cryptography_whitepaper.pdf "Cryptography Whitepaper")[Open Source](https://threema.ch/en/open-source "Open Source")[Blog](https://threema.ch/en/blog "Blog")

The Company[About](https://threema.ch/en/about "About")[Jobs](https://threema.ch/en/jobs "Jobs")[Transparency Report](https://threema.ch/en/transparencyreport "Transparency Report")[System Status](https://status.threema.ch/ "System Status")[Merch](https://threema.ch/en/fan-shop "Merch")

Contact[Support for individual users](https://threema.ch/en/support#contact "Support for individual users")[Support for companies](https://threema.ch/en/work/contact "Support for companies")[Press Material](https://threema.ch/en/press "Press Material")[Contact](https://threema.ch/en/contact "Contact")

Connect[Threema Channel](https://threema.ch/en/faq/Threema_Channel "Threema Channel")[Newsletter](https://threema.ch/en/newsletter "Newsletter")[Mastodon](https://mastodon.social/@threemaapp "Mastodon")[X](https://x.com/ThreemaApp "X")[Reddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/threema/ "Reddit")[GitHub](https://github.com/threema-ch "GitHub")

en

Made in Switzerland. © 2024 Threema GmbH. [Privacy Policy](https://threema.ch/en/privacy). [Impressum](https://threema.ch/en/impressum).
